[{"answer": "That's pretty close to it, Piers.", "docId": "121115pmt", "aSentId": 23, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 22}, {"answer": "Well, my reaction is that I think it's been very clear now for quite a long time that there was no demonstration and that of course was the key element in what Ambassador Rice was saying and what the president was saying, and all about this hateful video and the demonstrations that it triggered.", "docId": "121115pmt", "aSentId": 68, "question": "What is your reaction to this?", "qSentId": 67}, {"answer": "Well, I know this that on the same day when she was at all of these different Sunday shows, sent out by the White House and with talking points from the White House, immediate -- the show that I was on, \"Face the Nation,\" immediately after she gave her standard statement there, they -- Bob Schieffer had the president of the Libyan National Assembly on.", "docId": "121115pmt", "aSentId": 84, "question": "Do you dispute that she acted in good faith in reporting what she had been told by the CIA intelligence briefing?", "qSentId": 83}, {"answer": "Well, you covered a lot of territory there and I would like to point out I'm the guy that called for Rumsfeld to resign because the war in Iraq was going terribly.", "docId": "121115pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "And I suppose the obvious question is, is it fair to impugn the integrity of the U.N. ambassador if she was genuinely acting in good faith on the CIA briefing?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "Everybody should be accountable, Piers.", "docId": "121115pmt", "aSentId": 123, "question": "Clearly if the CIA had been inaccurately briefing for quite some time after this, do you believe that he should be accountable for the misinformation process?", "qSentId": 122}, {"answer": "Well, I think the whole area is unraveling.", "docId": "121115pmt", "aSentId": 133, "question": "What is your take on this and what do you think the American reaction should be, if anything?", "qSentId": 132}, {"answer": "You know, I don't know.", "docId": "121115pmt", "aSentId": 148, "question": "Should Mitt Romney be a little above this now and just take defeat gracefully?", "qSentId": 147}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121115pmt", "aSentId": 164, "question": "Over the fact you hadn't gone to a briefing about Benghazi, isn't it?", "qSentId": 163}, {"answer": "CCAIN: Sure.", "docId": "121115pmt", "aSentId": 170, "question": "Why you weren't at that meeting yesterday?", "qSentId": 169}, {"answer": "What we're seeing overhead is basically Israeli war planes flying towards the border with Gaza.", "docId": "121115pmt", "aSentId": 200, "question": "Fred, what's the latest there?", "qSentId": 199}, {"answer": "It's very difficult to assess who's at fault for this.", "docId": "121115pmt", "aSentId": 211, "question": "What is your sense of how this is playing out in the international stage?", "qSentId": 210}, {"answer": "Well, I won't get into military operations but it has to be very, very clear.", "docId": "121115pmt", "aSentId": 227, "question": "What are you hearing and what is the plan?", "qSentId": 226}, {"answer": "I want to make something perfectly clear.", "docId": "121115pmt", "aSentId": 242, "question": "What is the constructive way through this?", "qSentId": 241}, {"answer": "That's precisely it, Piers.", "docId": "121115pmt", "aSentId": 292, "question": "It's a dangerous cocktail, isn't it?", "qSentId": 291}, {"answer": "It's very much at risk.", "docId": "121115pmt", "aSentId": 313, "question": "Is that at risk?", "qSentId": 312}, {"answer": "First, one has to say, Piers, as you did, the Israelis are justified in doing something when all these rockets are being fired at them.", "docId": "121115pmt", "aSentId": 322, "question": "It's an awful place for people to try and live, isn't it?", "qSentId": 321}, {"answer": "I think it's very clear that the administration didn't handle things right from the start.", "docId": "121115pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "What do you make of that?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "Well, my reaction really for all of the elections around the country is it's really time to sort of evaluate what went right and what went wrong.", "docId": "121115pmt", "aSentId": 391, "question": "What was your reaction, honestly, to what Mitt Romney was saying there?", "qSentId": 390}, {"answer": "Well, look, Piers, you said something that frustrates me.", "docId": "121115pmt", "aSentId": 407, "question": "If I was a black or Hispanic or female voter, I would be like, hang on a second, he's saying what, we've been bought?", "qSentId": 406}, {"answer": "Well, look, what's important about Benghazi is to really get to the heart of the matter, truly understand what went wrong.", "docId": "121115pmt", "aSentId": 445, "question": "In the spirit of cooperation, how do you feel about somebody like Senator McCain making it so personal towards Ambassador Rice about what happened in Benghazi?", "qSentId": 444}, {"answer": "Thank you.", "docId": "121115pmt", "aSentId": 455, "question": "What are you going to do next?", "qSentId": 454}, {"answer": "Well, he was that.", "docId": "121115pmt", "aSentId": 491, "question": "What was he to you?", "qSentId": 490}, {"answer": "Yeah, I mean if it was like choosing a favorite child, then I would have been the most profligate woman on the planet.", "docId": "121115pmt", "aSentId": 521, "question": "What would it be?", "qSentId": 520}, {"answer": "As somebody who said, which he said in the front of the -- the beginning of his memoir, \"Hitch 22,\" \"live all you can.", "docId": "121115pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "How do you think he would have liked to have been remembered?", "qSentId": 529}]